TIP096
内海⑳カーリー
Utsumi Kali
内海卡莉
paragraph_count:4
init_addr:7dcc
pc_index:TIP_104

#PARAGRAPHS_JP:
#JP#1
;7dd0;192;氏名：内海⑳カーリー／Utsumi Kali%N
性別：女%N
年齢：27歳%N
誕生日：1984年９月16日（Virgo）%N
血液型：Ｏ型%N
職業：公立小学校の教師（裏設定：休職中）%N
知力：高い%N
体力：平均的%N
協調性：極めて高い%N

#JP#2
;7dd4;300;性格：とにかく優しい%N
⑳（時には行き過ぎて過保護になる）%N
⑳涙脆いが芯は強い%N
⑳キレると凄まじく怖い%N
趣味：料理・家庭菜園・壷集め%N
好き：世話を焼くこと・人の話を聞くこと%N
⑳大自然・心臓の音・おちゃめな冗談%N
嫌い：死を匂わせる言動や思想%N
⑳自然を破壊する行為・人を見捨てる行為%N
設定：インド系ハーフ%N

#JP#3
;7dd8;340;裏設定：『グレートマザー（太母）』を%N
⑳象徴する（→元型）%N
⑳黄泉木の妻。ふたりの間には%N
⑳子供がいたが、数年前の虐殺事件の%N
⑳被害者となり、死亡している%N
⑳犯人の名前は「犬伏景子」%N
⑳子供の死が原因で心を病んでいて、%N
⑳数ヶ月前まで精神病院に入院していた%N
⑳2011年８月に出産。生まれた子供は双子%N
⑳（二卵性双生児）この設定は2012年のもの%N

#JP#4
;7ddc;240;主にスフィアサイドに登場。%N
悟と同じく、あるスフィアに滞在中。%N
博識で、特に心理学に精通している。%N
グループのムードメーカーにして、まとめ役。%N
なぜか時々、言動の中に不可解なものが%N
見え隠れする。%N
犬伏景子に対して、憎悪の念を抱いている。%N


#PARAGRAPHS_TRANSLATED:
#EN#1
Full Name: Utsumi Kali%N
Sex: Female%N
Age: 27%N
Birthday: September 16th, 1984 (Virgo)%N
Blood Type: O%N
Occupation: Public school teacher%N
(Beyond the surface: temporarily retired)%N
Intelligence: High%N
Physical Strength: Average%N
Cooperativeness: Extremely high%N

#EN#2
Personality: Generally gentle and kind (sometimes goes overboard and borders on pampering).%N
Easily moved to tears, but strong at heart.%N
Incredibly scary when she snaps.%N
Hobbies: Cooking, gardening, collecting vases%N
Likes: Meddling in others' business, listening to other people's stories, nature, the sound of the heartbeat, silly jokes%N
Dislikes: Things that make her think of death, actions that are harmful to nature, forsaking people%N
Background: Half-Indian%N

#EN#3
Beyond the Surface: Represents the "Great Mother" (→ Archetype)%N
Yomogi's wife. They had a child, but he became one of the victims of the mass murder incident several years ago, dying at the hands of Inubushi Keiko.%N
The loss of her child has caused her great psychological suffering which is why, until several months ago, she was institutionalized in a psychiatric hospital.%N
In August 8th, 2011, she gave birth.%N
The newborns are (fraternal) twins.%N
This is her status as of 2012.%N

#EN#4
Utsumi Kali mainly appears in the SPHIA side of the story.%N
Like Satoru, she is one of the inmates of SPHIA.%N
She possesses extensive knowledge, especially in the field of psychology.%N
She is the mood maker and the mediator of the group.%N
For some reason, she says and does some very strange things from time to time.%N
She bears a great hatred toward Inubushi Keiko.

#CN#1
姓名：内海卡莉%N
性别：女%N
年龄：27岁%N
生日：1984年9月16日（处女座）%N
血型：O型%N
职业：公立小学教师（设定：停职中）%N
智力：较高%N
体力：普通%N
协调性：极高%N

#CN#2
性格：慈祥（有时会变成溺爱）、%N
⑳爱流泪却很坚强、发怒后十分恐怖%N
兴趣：料理、家庭菜园、收集罐子%N
喜好：照顾别人、听别人说话、%N
大自然、心脏跳动的声音、调皮的玩笑%N
厌恶：暗示着死亡的行动与思想、%N
⑳破坏自然的行为、抛弃他人的行为%N
设定：印度混血儿%N

#CN#3
里设定：象征“Great Mother（大母神）”（→原型）%N
⑳黄泉木圣司的妻子。%N
⑳虽然两人曾经生下小孩，%N
⑳但却在数年前作为虐杀事件的受害者死亡。%N
⑳凶手的名字是“犬伏景子”。%N
⑳孩子的死亡是她心病的起因，%N
⑳几个月前进入精神病院疗养。%N
⑳2011年8月生下一对双胞胎（异卵双胞胎）。%N
%N
这是针对2012年的设定。%N

主要在SPHIA登场。%N
与优希堂悟一样居住在SPHIA中。%N
博学多闻，尤其精通心理学。%N
是团体气氛的领导者，仲裁者。%N
在她的话语、行动背后，%N
不知道为什么常常会隐藏着一些令人无法了解的深意。%N
对犬伏景子抱持憎恨。%N

